

# Lilian Adel Zaki Armanious

### **Personal Data:**

• **Birth Date:** 8<sup>th</sup> of May - 1982

• **Nationality:** Egyptian.

• Marital Status: Married (No Children).

• Address: Sheraton Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt.

• **Mobile**: (+2) 0100-2043807

• **Skype ID**: lilian799211

• Email: <u>liliadel75@gmail.com</u>

## **Career Summary:**

I have more than 15 years of experience in Administration, Customer service and Marketing. I have done it all – filing, faxing, copying, making spreadsheets, entering data, answering multiple phone lines and emails, using different platform systems like (SAP and CRM) .. Etc. I am quite flexible in the work I do. I am able to take on multiple tasks easily and I am able to learn new skills quickly and effectively. I consider myself a hard worker who is easy to get along with (I can provide excellent recommendations in that regard!). I always have a positive attitude because I believe that negativity in any area of your life is just useless and detrimental to what can be accomplished. I consider myself to be highly organized and capable of taking on the tasks handed to me; my resume outlines my skills and knowledge, in addition to my Marketing and Social Media experiences.

## **Educational Background:**

- <u>High School Year 2000</u>: "Notre Dames Des Apôtres" (English Section)
- Bachelor degree of Commerce and Business Administration, English Section -Year 2005, Helwan University.

**Major:** Business Administration and Foreign Trade "English section".

Grade: Good Honor.

## **Languages Skills:**

- Competency in written and spoken English.
- Competency in written & spoken Arabic.
- Familiar with written French.

### **Computer Skills:**

- Proficient in Microsoft Suite.
- Excellent knowledge of windows in its various versions and Microsoft office Word, Excel, Internet, E-mail, Power point, Outlook, Operation of fax and Photocopier, SAP System and Photoshop.

## **Acknowledgments and Awards:**

- Received a "**Thank you letter**" from Mr. Ahmed Abou Douma, former Director of Marketing Department Mobinil for "The internal focus group" idea that I came up with.
- An **Internal focus group** is a form of internal qualitative research that is held internally between the Marketing and the Customer Service Departments in particular in which a group of our best agents are questioned about the customers' attitude towards a product, service or a concept. Questions are asked in an interactive group setting where participants are free to talk with other group members and hence it is to be considered an important tool for acquiring feedback.
  - Nominated several times for "Agent of the month" for showing accuracy and professionalism of handling different customer inquiries.
  - Received **recognition vouchers** for achieving Exceptional performance levels.

#### **Trainings:**

- International Service Checker Certificate, May 2018
- Code of Conduct "Novartis Pharmaceuticals", December 2014
- Responsible and Compliant use of Social Media "Novartis Pharmaceuticals", December 2014
- Adverse Events, "Novartis Pharmaceuticals", November 2014
- IMS Training (Integrated Management System), December 2013
- Integrated Customer Relations [95%], JP Morgan international, April 2010
- "Presentation Skills", OMNI Training Center, June 2008
- "Personal Effectiveness", Quest Education Center for Human Development, May 2008
- "Negotiation Skills", Quest Education Center for Human Development, November 2006
- "Customer Handling and Body Language", Mobinil Telecommunications, September 2005
- "Computer Based Courses" IBM International, September 2002

#### **Competencies:**

- Able to work on own initiative and as part of a team.
- Exceptional Organization and Customer Service Skills
- Strong verbal and written communication skills.

- Ability to think creatively, solve problems, take decisions, knows how to learn, and reason.
- High level of initiative and assertiveness.
- Ability to present work quickly and accurately.
- Detail Orientated, Accurate, Flexible and Reliable.
- Ability to Develop, Execute and Integrate.
- High level of presentation skills
- Time Management.
- Excellent interpersonal skills.
- Tact and discretion to handle price sensitive or highly confidential information.
- Motivated and flexible for training, travel, extra working hours, etc.
- Ability to react quickly and work under heavy pressure while remaining calm and Controlled.

## **Work Experiences:**

## From 03/2021 till present: HSBC Bank in the Digital Business Services Center as:

## **Executive Assistant to Senior Strategic Change Director Europe**

- To provide high quality, confidential and comprehensive administrative, analytical support.
- Duties to include diary management, email handling, expense management, administration of leadership meetings and other key committees, scheduling appointments, planning and structuring programs and itineraries across different time zones.
- Be responsible for calendar management for the Senior Manager, requiring interaction with internal and external executives and assistants, to coordinate a variety of meetings
- Communicate and handle incoming and outgoing emails on behalf of the Senior Manager and respond where appropriate
- Promptly screen and handle daily calls and inquiries and respond independently to routine issues and questions
- Make travel arrangements for the Senior Manager and arrange overseas meeting schedule and programs
- Take minutes of meetings and follow up with any actions.
- Produce letters, reports, memoranda, forms and schedules, utilizing various PC-based software package.
- Perform general clerical duties to include but not limited to: photocopying, faxing, mailing, handling courier and filing; and sometimes confidential materials
- Team administration to consolidate department organization charts, staff contacts, holiday records, and the whereabouts.

#### From 03/2016 till 05/2018: Baker and Mckenzie International Law firm as:

#### Personal Assistant to the Partner.

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- Day to day duties including filtering, sorting and printing emails, photocopying, faxing, mailing, scanning and handling phone calls.
- Handling correspondence: open e-mails and letters, revise them, sort them and reply to them according to the instructions of the Partner.
- Preparing documentation (creating, editing and formatting documents, agreements, and opinion letters, due diligence reports, presentations and charts).
- Creating and maintaining filing system and keeping track of current, closed and archived files.
- Electronic filing/archiving for emails.
- Managing partner's agenda (scheduling appointments, meetings, conferences); maintaining and updating partner's task list, reminders and monitoring projects deadlines.
- Meeting arrangements/catering.. etc.
- Marketing: prepare partner's personalized marketing materials such as IFLR and Chambers submissions and coordinate with marketing personnel on it.
- Conducting Internet and Baker Web search.

#### Billing

- Entering and closing partner's timesheet.
- Attending to Potential Clients: preparing proposals, capability statements, fee estimates and pitches.
- Attending to New Clients: Conducting conflict checks, preparing proposals, conflict alerts, engagement letters, assignment letters, consent letters.
- Filing CMIS forms and preparing NBRs.
- Handling Client Credit submissions; following up on awards and filing for appeals, if necessary.
- Billing: Review/amend draft pre-bills, edit and print invoices and follow up on payment. Respond to clients inquiries regarding invoices.
- Making travel and hotel arrangements and reservations and filling in visa applications.
- Translation.
- All other secretarial work required.

## From 11/2013 - 01/2016: Novartis Pharmaceuticals Company as:

### **Executive Assistant to the Marketing and Sales Director.**

- Coordinating director's diary & planning his meetings.
- Handling all the meetings and conference calls outside or inside the company.
- Create filling system and ensure that documents files are kept in track up to date.
- Compose and types correspondence on the company templates.
- Reviewing the correspondences before signature.

- Type letters, reports, presentations and other documents.
- Acting independently as the principal administrative support for the Operations Director, including managing the agenda, mailbox, contacts database management and expenses.
- Providing optimal and time effective travel arrangements to the Operations Director.
- Maintain office supplies and equipment; order supplies for staff as needed.
- Involved in financial aspects of the Operations department; prepares and submits expense reports, monitors departmental expenditures, assists in preparation of budget. Responsible for overseeing faculty payroll processing.
- Creation & Follow up for the following major items: (Local & International Events, Cycle Meeting activities, Market researches, Speakers Honorariums & Special Requests).
- Direct Communication & Follow up with Conference Organizers to ensure all required documents are furnished on time as per the finance department.
- Direct Communication & Follow up with District Sales Managers regarding the details arrangements involved in the organization of local/international conferences & events.
- Direct Communication with Travel agencies to ensure the complete proper implementation of all marketing managed events on time.
- Direct Communication & Follow up with the purchasing department regarding printed materials &market research until the issuance of the purchase order.
- Direct Communication with the Advertising agencies to make the necessary changes of the ads/campaigns according to the DRA & medical comments.
- Develop and install the process for execution of Speakers Payments.
- Managing receivable of invoices & issuing the payment orders for marketing magazines, Ads, Conferences, 3<sup>rd</sup> party services ... etc.\
- Support all requests related to Field Force Marketing and Sales activities.
- Arranging Pity Cash for adhoc business demands.
- Manages courier and parcels.
- Manages and overlooks office boy and messenger activities.
- Collect Visa Credentials for invitees and making sure it's handed to the organizer on time to issue the visa.
- Issue visa Invitation Letters for doctors and keep a track of it.
- Ensure Files & Records are maintained in accordance with legal requirements and company policies and procedures.
- Finalize accruals for all brands at the end of each month as per the timelines provided by the finance.
- Support all requests related to Field Force sales activities.
- Track spending per brand per specialty per line and provide a complete report before the end of each month.
- Update and coordinated the SOPs regulations for the whole company.
- Provide continuous update for all events and personal business meetings and vacations on the calendar on regular basis.

## From 03/2011 - 10/2013: Vodafone International Services as:

### **International Account Senior Advisor and Admin Support (UK Account)**

- Facilitate and provide a Vodafone global customer service standard.
- Own and manage the client relationship: resolving calls efficiently and effectively.
- Ensure service level agreements are met and maintained.

- Work as part of a team to ensure offering world-class Customer Service at all times.
- Be proactive in regards to the improvement of processes and procedures.
- Communicate positively with all involved parties in order to facilitate customer's reception of the expected distinguished service.
- Create and promote an environment that fosters both individual and team advancement to ensure the outstanding delivery of customer service.
- Mentor and support new employees.
- Meeting service level in handling all transactions measured through productivity reports.
- Accuracy in handling all assigned tasks.
- Performing Administrative Functions.
- Maintain professional work relationships with colleagues, supervisor and manager.
- Presentation preparation (PowerPoint slides, handout compilation Oral and written Communication.
- Use available methods & tools to develop own skills & information (applications, intranet briefings, attending trainings....etc.)
- Escalate problems & provides relevant feedback to the right channels.
- Contribute to the up selling of Vodafone's Products and Services through the NBA project.
- Attends meetings and responsible for preparing meeting agenda and minutes of meeting.
- Producing documents, briefing papers, reports and presentations.

### From 05/2005 - 12/2010: Mobinil Telecommunication as:

## **Executive Secretary to Head of Operations.**

- Preparing the agendas & translating the minute of meetings.
- Organizing Events and Conference Calls.
- Practical arrangement of meetings to be on time.
- Presentation preparation (PowerPoint slides, handout compilation).
- Coordinating director diary & planning his meetings.
- Handling all the meetings and conference calls outside the company or inside.
- Create filling system and ensure that documents files are kept in track up to date.
- Comply with the company procedures by ensuring the documents are composed, dispatched, and circulated.
- Compose and types correspondence on the company templates.
- Reviewing the correspondences before signature.
- Type letters, reports, presentations and other documents.
- Handling incoming & outgoing, mails, Faxes & Phone Calls.
- Assist planning/coordinating major events.
- Involved in financial aspects of the Operations department; prepares and submits expense
  reports, monitors departmental expenditures, assists in preparation of budget. Responsible for
  overseeing faculty payroll processing.
- Accountable for the day to day operational management within the agreed budgets and the strategic development of all operational services within the specified operational management portfolio, balancing the need for proactive service development and strategic leadership against reactive demands of operational responsibilities.
- Handles all office related issues as office supplies, utility bills, office setup and cleaning.
- Manages courier and parcels.

- Coordinate for some brands marketing campaigns.
- Support updating the intranet of the company in the Planning Process department.
- Arrange for Marketing Campaigns.
- Manages and updates company contacts databases and business cards.
- Manages petty cash and reports expenses to accounting department.
- Keeps employee records, and follows up time attendance and permissions.
- Support updating the intranet of the company.

#### **References:**

Furnished upon request.